[THUMPING IN DISTANCE]
[MAN PANTING]
[ANIMAL GROWLING]
[GROANING]
Trevor!
Max.
[CAR HORN BEEPING]
Whoa, whoa.
Although Wegener was ridiculed
by the scientific community...
...he was eνentually found
to be correct...
...in his theory of an original
supercontinent called Pangaea.
[BELL RINGS]
Yeah. Okay.
Ah. Come to papa.
TREVOR:
Hey, Leonard.
LEONARD:
Hey, man.
-Dude, you ain't gonna be happy.
-Why?
-It's Kitzens.
-I see.
-Hello.
-Trevor, there's my favorite colleague.
-How are you, Alan?
-l'm good.
-How's that Con Drift class of yours going?
-Fine.
Does it get echoey in there
with so few students?
[TREVOR CHUCKLES]
So, what do you got on the books?
l'm busy.
No, no, I can see how busy you are.
So I'll try to be
as quick as possible here.
The university is pulling the plug
on your brother's lab.
Pulling the plug?
Yeah, it's gonna finally give us
all the storage space we need.
Let's get something straight here,
this facility is dedicated...
...to the research of Maxwell Anderson's
theories predicting the volcanic fissures--
Which have never been proven.
I mean, how many of your late brother's
sensors are even still active? One, two--?
-Three.
-lt used to be 29.
This is the wrong time to shut us down.
I have got seismic activity in Bolivia.
I got a 13 millimeter shift in Mongolia.
Alan, you can't shut us down.
Keep the lab open.
-It's all I've got left of Max.
-lt's been 10 years since Max, Trevor.
I am sorry about all this. I really am.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
WOMAN [ON RECORDlNG]:
Trevor, are you there? lt's Elizabeth.
Pick up, please.
Okay. Well, uh, we are on the 95,
and were heading your way.
You wanna say hi
to your Uncle Trevor, Sean?
BOY:
No.
WOMAN: Just say hello.
-No.
BOY: I don't want to.
-Oh, no.
WOMAN:
Hey, it's your sister-in-law again.
Just wanted to make sure
what time you'd be home...
...because well be there around 6.
Okay. Well, we'll be on my cell.
-Oh, boy.
-Sean's looking forward to seeing you.
-Right, Sean?
BOY: Negatory.
WOMAN: I'm getting worried that
we mightuve gotten our signals crossed.
Please call me.
[PHONE RINGS]
TREVOR [ON RECORDING]:
I'm not home. Leave me a message.
WOMAN: Trevor, we're pulling up
in front of your building.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
Trevor, you in there?
TREVOR:
Hi.
-Hey.
-How are you, Elizabeth?
-Oh, you're home.
-lt's so good to see you.
You too.
-How are you? I just got your messages.
-Uh-huh.
-You forgot, didn't you?
-I didn't forget.
How could I forget?
-You didn't forget?
-l....
I forgot.
It doesn't mean I haven't been...
...looking forward
to time with my nephew.
I haven't seen him since he was 9?
-Seven.
-Wow. Ha-ha.
So how long
is he gonna be staying again?
-Ten days.
-Is that what we said?
Hey, Sean. How are you?
Looking good.
-ls that one of those Game Boys?
-lt's a PSP.
-Cool.
-Sean, get up, say hi to your uncle.
Hi to your uncle.
Last time I saw you,
you were about this high.
-Oh! Ha-ha.
-Yeah, good one.
You got that?
Okay, you've got all my numbers.
You've got your ticket
and passport in your bag.
I will be there to pick you up in Ottawa.
And by then I'll have found us a house
and we can start on this big new adventure.
-Pretty exciting stuff, huh?
SEAN: Yeah, it's great.
We get to be Canadians. Thrilling, eh?
Just Iet yourself in.
-It will be good for him, being with you.
-Yeah.
Who knows?
Maybe it will be good for you too.
This is for you.
What--? ls this Sean's?
No, it's Max's.
-Max's?
-Yeah.
So, hey, dude. This is gonna be fun.
A couple of dudes hanging out.
Five days, maybe a week.
You know, doing dude stuff,
what dudes do.
You like baseball?
You know what we should do?
We should go get in a batting cage.
Yeah, okay, listen.
l don't like this any more than you do.
As long as you keep stocked
with Mountain Dew...
...and TiVo Family Guy,
we'll get along fine.
-Sure.
-Oh, wow.
-That's an awesome coin collection.
-Oh.
Well, kind of a pet project of mine.
-Yeah, it's really nifty.
-Thanks.
You hungry?
We could order in, you know.
Maybe some pizza, Chinese, Thai food?
Subs? Or something Iike that?
-Wow.
-What's that?
Well, it's a box of possessions
of a really great guy.
Your dad.
His old ball glove.
Mom doesn't talk about him very much.
Well, you can take my word for it.
He was one of those few people...
...who are just exceptional
at everything they do.
Ooh. You see this?
This was your old man's PSP.
-A yo-yo?
-Don't be dissing the yo-yo.
This is physics at work.
You got your centrifugal force.
Your gravitational pull,
you got your potential energy.
And in ancient times, did you know...
...that this was actually used
as a hunting impIement?
Watch.
-Hey, here, let me try.
-Yeah, you should probably take it.
l have no idea what this is.
Hello.
This was his favorite book.
JuIes Verne's
A Journey to the Center of the Earth.
You know, l think that was
on my summer reading list once.
-l never got to it.
-That's too bad, it's a good read.
To him, it wasn't just science fiction,
it was inspiration.
He used to read this to me
when l was a really little kid.
Hello. What are these notes?
"Magma temperatures reach 1 1 50
in Mongolia"?
"Bolivia."
"Hawaii."
Look out!
Hey, Sean, let's go check out my Iab.
SEAN:
So it couldn't wait for tomorrow?
TREVOR:
Your dad used to say:
"Tectonophysics is the science of now,
not tomorrow."
lt's about seismic events
that occur in an instant.
Here, look at this.
You got Hawaii, Bolivia, MongoIia.
And the conditions today are almost
exactly what they were in July '97.
What's the big deal about July '97?
Sean, that was the year
that your dad went missing.
Now, look, you see this column
of numbers here?
lf the 753, right here, was a 752,
then it would be....
Exactly the same.
What do these little blips mean?
Don't touch anything.
Those Iittle blips are my life's work.
These four littIe blips
are your entire life's work?
Three. Three little blips.
One, two, three, four.
lceland.
This makes sense.
Max saw the readings 1 0 years ago,
and he took off to investigate.
Now, if the readings are the same today
as they were then...
...this may be my only chance
to find out what happened.
-l'm gonna need your passport.
-For what?
l'm sorry, l have to get you to Canada
a little earlier than we planned.
What are you talking about?
l'm talking about this.
A Journey to the Center of the Earth.
lt's all set in Iceland,
which is where he must've gone.
These are all my dad's notes?
Look...
...Max and I--
Your dad and l were talking about
the possibility of νolcanic tubes existing...
...that went down past the mantIe,
towards the center of the Earth.
And that's what I think
he went looking for.
Sorry, l gotta put you on a flight
to Ottawa in the morning.
-And l'm calling Icelandair.
-No, no, look.
-Hey.
-l just got here, okay?
You're not gonna go and ditch me.
l was the person who found your life's work
fourth little blip thingy in the first place.
-This is my brother we're taIking about.
-lt's my dad.
Now, I don't have to be in Ottawa
for 1 0 days. l'm going with you.
Know how much to book
a last-minute flight to Reykjavik?
Something tells me you got it covered.
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN lCELANDIC
OVER SPEAKERS]
TREVOR: "Descend, boId traveler,
into the crater of the jokul of Sneffels...
...which the shadow of Scartaris touches
before the kalends of JuIy...
...and you will attain
the center of the Earth."
Ooh.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
l'm deciphering these notations
that your father made in this book.
l think there's a code
behind the pairing of letters.
lt might haνe something to do
with the periodic table.
For instance, I've got S-A, I-S, G-G.
l belieνe that P-B is on the periodic table
and that's plumbum.
-Plumbum means lead.
-What's "Sigurbjörn Ásgeirsson"?
What?
Well, it's right here. Read it down.
Sigurbjörn Àsgeirsson.
Oh. Uh....
Sigurbjörn Àsgeirsson, that's....
That's a clue. Maybe that's a place.
lt could be a thing.
-What are you doing?
-l am Googling at 30,000 feet.
-Are you supposed to be doing that?
-Welcome to the 21 st century.
-Okay. Here.
-lt's a person.
"Sigurbjörn Ásgeirsson,
executiνe director...
...of Ásgeirsson lnstitute
for Progressive Volcanology."
Max would've known this guy.
l knew it was a good thing to bring you.
His institute has gotta be our first stop.
SEAN:
Are we there yet?
TREVOR:
lf you mean annoying, yeah, we're there.
-You know, you're going kind of slow.
-l'm going kind of safe.
l just saw a goat in the passing lane.
When's the whole adventure thing
gonna begin?
Let me give you something fun to do.
Navigate.
Where are we?
Have we passed Haνanschlicht?
-Havanschlicht?
-Yeah.
l don't know.
Have we passed Eingarsstadir?
-l don't know.
-Reyniνír?
-Húsavik?
TREVOR: No.
SEAN: GrundarhoI?
SEAN: Stifflarschtarder?
TREVOR:
Stifflardschtarder?
SEAN: How about Koldukardarskinoquue?
TREVOR: What?
SEAN: We're definitely lost.
TREVOR: We're not Iost.
Just Iook for an institution.
SEAN: What's an institution look like?
-l don't know, it looks big and institutional.
lt's gotta be around here somewhere.
Hey, look, there's a littIe shack up there.
We can stop there and ask for directions.
-We're not lost.
-Oh, no, definitely not.
What's this? A ski shack?
"Àsgeirsson...
[TREVOR MUMBLING]
...Institute for Progressiνe Volcanology."
l told you I'd find it.
Alrighty.
-Not too shabby.
-All right.
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN lCELANDIC]
Oh, I'm sorry, l don't speak Icelandic.
-Hi, can I help you?
-Hello.
-l'm Hannah.
-Oh, how do you do? Hi.
l'm Trev-- Professor Anderson.
l'm visiting from America. Um....
-This is Sean, my nephew.
-l'm Sean.
Hi, Sean.
l was wondering if l could
possibly speak with, forgive me here...
...Sigurbjörn Àsgeirsson?
Um....
Well, Sigurbjörn Àsgeirsson is dead.
-Dead?
-Yeah, he died three winters ago.
Oh. Uh....
So do you run the institute?
Nobody does. There is no institute.
-There's a sign down the road that says--
-Progressive volcanology was a failed idea.
Like, you know, the Berlin Wall
and eight-track tapes.
l see.
Well, did you work with him?
No, no. He was my father.
Yeah? l know it. What about it?
Well, this book belonged
to my late brother, Max.
Max Anderson?
We believe that he may have been
in contact with your father.
-Your brother was a Vernian.
-What's a Vernian?
Someone that believes that the writings
of Jules Verne were actual fact.
l mean, the guy
was a science fiction writer.
And yet this society of believers
regarded Verne like a visionary.
My father
was the biggest Vernian of them all.
My brother was no Vernian.
This was my father's copy.
Take a look.
See, the markings are exactly the same.
Your brother was a Vernian.
Wow, my dad was kind of out there.
-You didn't know him, Sean.
-l'm starting to think you didn't either.
He was no member
of some secret society.
-What are you guys doing here?
-l'm a scientist, l'm a professor.
l'm here because there are seismic sensors
going off 30 klicks north of here...
...that we think
that we should check into.
And that's the reason that we're here,
plain and simple.
Okay.
You know,
there are no roads to the north.
Well....
l'm a mountain guide.
l can take you there, professor.
-Great.
-That's great, I loνe hiking.
-l would appreciate that. That'd be great.
-Good.
-Call me Treνor.
-You can call me Sean.
So it will be 5000 kronur to go up there.
Five grand a day? No problem.
An hour.
Do you accept rolls of quarters?
Come on, boys.
l wanna be home by sundown.
TREVOR: Hey, you think you can slow down
a little bit, please?
-Dibs.
-What?
l got dibs on the mountain guide.
-You're 1 3.
-Sorry, called it.
-Thirteen-year-olds don't get dibs.
-Get over it.
We're getting closer.
All right, just watch your step there.
Mount Sneffels is deceptively treacherous.
-What's Sneffels?
-Well, why don't you tell him, professor?
SneffeIs is the name of the mountain
where this character Liedenbrock...
...apparently found a portal
to the center of the Earth.
Let's just find that sensor of yours,
professor.
TREVOR:
There it is.
Yes.
HANNAH:
Well, what do you need to do with it?
l gotta unlock it.
lt's got, like, a black box...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
...that has recorded
all of the seismic activity...
...that's transpired in the last 1 0 years.
Could tell me a lot about Max.
And what he was doing
when he went missing.
Trevor, l'm really sorry,
we're gonna haνe to go now.
Must be corroded.
Trevor, we need to-- Whoa.
Okay, we need to take cover.
Come on, Sean. Right now.
l'll be right there.
-Trevor, just Ieave it for now.
TREVOR: l'νe almost got it.
HANNAH:
We need to take cover now.
Come on. Trevor.
-Uncle Trevor.
-Get in here.
-Yes. Oh!
HANNAH: Watch out.
Hurry up. Come on.
Trevor,
the sensor's attracting the lightning.
-Drop it. Drop the sensor.
TREVOR: What? I'm not gonna drop it.
SEAN: Hurry!
HANNAH: lt's attracting the lightning!
[TREVOR SCREAMlNG]
[COUGHlNG]
Trevor?
-Trevor?
TREVOR: l'm all right.
[TREVOR GROANlNG]
HANNAH:
Sean?
-Sean, you all right?
-l'm good.
-Okay, everybody, just stay calm.
SEAN: Guys, come on, you gotta help me dig.
Come on.
-Forget it, it's no use.
-Forget it?
TREVOR:
She's right.
There must be about 60 or 70 tons
of boulders on top of us.
Take us about a month
to dig out of here.
-We have to find another way.
-What if there is no other way?
There's always another way, Sean.
What else have you got?
Signal fIares, first aid, some rope, blankets
and a couple of protein bars.
But they're on a ration.
-Don't know how Iong we'll be trapped for.
-Trapped? ls that what we are?
She-- No, she didn't mean that.
-Sean, hey, what are you doing?
-God, l'm not getting any service.
Sean, you're not gonna get any signal
down here, okay?
Put this away.
Okay, don't worry about it.
-We'll find another way out, all right?
HANNAH: Okay.
One of these
might snake back to the surface.
How do we know which one to take?
My gut says we go right.
Come on.
Looks promising.
Just put one foot in front of the other.
We'll be out of here in no time.
Looking good.
Don't worry, direction is my sixth sense.
Pay attention, Sean.
lt's just like doing field work.
l used to love doing field work.
[GASPS]
-Watch out.
-Ah!
You're not studying rocks in a lab,
professor.
-This is life or death here.
-Yeah, thanks.
You owe me one.
What does this say?
[SPEAKS lN ICELANDIC]
That means keep out.
-Maybe that's decent advice.
-No, no. This is great news.
This might Iead us to an oId mine shaft
and that could be our way out.
-How deep do you think it is?
-Can you give me one of those flares?
Thank you. Sean, Iook at your watch.
l'm gonna light this
and drop it over the edge...
...and I want you to tell me
how many seconds pass before it stops.
Okay.
Here we go. Three, two....
Oh, God!
HANNAH:
What?
What was that?
Yup, magnesium.
Must run in veins
all through these walls.
Magnesium is kind of flammable,
isn't it, professor?
Yeah, used in flares,
used in gun powder, matchsticks.
Right, well, maybe gun powders and flares
aren't such a good idea down here.
Thank you.
lt's the same principle.
-You ready, Sean?
SEAN: Yeah, go ahead.
Three, two....
One.
Two.
[THUDS]
Almost three.
Thirty-two squared by-- lt's 200 feet.
That's no problem.
lt's about your basic 20-story high-rise.
-You got enough rope?
-l always have enough rope.
Well, no problem for what?
Rappelling down in there.
We're gonna rappel down
that deep, dark hoIe?
What, you got a problem with that?
-Pfft.
-What's the matter?
There's no way
we should be rappelling down.
What are you talking about? You're
man enough to call dibs on the guide.
-But not enough to climb down a rope.
HANNAH: Guys.
-Calling dibs on the mountain guide--
-No one gets dibs on the mountain guide.
We're going down there.
HANNAH:
Steady, steady.
Remember, we're all connected.
lt's okay.
TREVOR:
Looking good.
lt's all good down here.
Way down here.
You guys are coming down, right?
All right, Sean, l'm gonna start
lowering you down really, really slowly.
So just Iean back
and keep your feet up high.
You're okay, Sean.
We're tethered together,
so nothing bad is gonna happen.
SEAN:
Yeah, sure.
HANNAH:
Good.
Sean, keep waIking.
You have to keep walking.
Good.
TREVOR:
Hey, you're looking pretty good there.
-Sure you haven't done this before?
-Shut up.
Hey, you mind?
Watch your step, will you?
l'm hanging on for my life here.
Okay, Sean,
just make conversation with me.
So, Hannah, do you come here often?
TREVOR:
Oh, give me a break.
That can't be the best line
you can come up with.
-l'm making conversation with her.
-No, Sean, l do not come here very often.
Ready?
Hey.
Look at all this schist.
-What?
-lt's a metamorphic rock.
Green schist, garnet schist,
mica-garnet schist.
-Oh. Schist.
-lt's everywhere, look at it. I guess--
[TREVOR SCREAMlNG]
Trevor.
[HANNAH SCREAMS]
HANNAH: Get to the wall, Trevor.
TREVOR: l can't.
-l can't, the walls widen out down here.
-Your rope is caught on mine.
You're gonna take us down.
l gotta cut you loose.
TREVOR: What?
-Hannah, no.
Wait a minute, wait, wait, wait.
-Don't.
TREVOR: Don't, don't, don't.
-Uncle Trevor.
-Ah!
[GRUNTS]
Hey, guys, found it.
The bottom's right here.
Hey, Hannah, you knew that, right?
Right?
Hannah?
Guys, what's this?
TREVOR: Looks like
an abandoned mine tunnel to me.
That's Old Bla'giIs Mine.
lt was shut down 60 years ago
after the big disaster.
Disaster?
How big?
Eighty-one dead.
That's pretty big.
Come on.
Cowboy up.
SEAN: Hey, Trevor,
was there a mine like this in the book?
TREVOR:
No, don't think so.
-Hannah?
HANNAH: Yup?
TREVOR:
Can I ask you something?
هذا صحيح، حسناً، ربما البارود والطلقات الضوئية
ليست فكرة جيدة هنا
شكراً
إنه نفس المبدأ
هل أنت مستعد، يا (شون)؟ -
نعم، هيا -
... ثلاثة، إثنان
واحد
اثنان
تقريباً ثلاثة
اثنان وثلاثون الجذر التربيعي لـ ... إنها 200 قدم
لا يوجد مشكلة
إن عمقها بارتفاع 20 طابق
ألديكِ حبال كافية؟ -
دائماً لدي حبال كافية -
حسناً، لا يوجد مشكلة بالنسبة لماذا؟
النزول هناك
هل سننزل في تلك الحفرة العميقة المظلمة؟
ماذا؟ هل لديك مشكلة في هذا؟
ما المشكلة؟
لا يمكن أن ننزل في تلك الحفرة
ماذا تقول؟ أنت رجل بما فيه الكفاية
للمطالبة بحقك في مرشدة الجبال
ولكن ليس بما فيه الكفاية للنزول على حبل -
يا رفاق -
... المطالبة بحقي في مرشدة الجبال -
لا أحد له حق في مرشدة الجبال -
سنهبط هناك
اثبت، اثبت
تذكروا، إننا مربوطين ببعضنا
حسناً
يبدو هذا جيداً
كل شيء بخير بأسفل هنا
أنا أهبط لأسفل
ستنزلان هنا، يا رفاق، أليس كذلك؟
(حسناً، يا (شون
سوف أبدأ بإنزالك ببطء شديد جداً
لذلك فقط انحني للخلف
وأبقي قدميك بأعلى
(لا يوجد مشكلة، يا (شون
نحن مربوطون ببعضنا
لذلك لن يصيبنا مكروه
نعم، بالتأكيد
حسناً
شون)، استمر في السير)
يجب أن تستمر في السير
جيد
أنت تبدو جيداً هناك
هل أنت متأكد أنك لم تفعل هذا من قبل؟ -
!اخرس -
اسمع، هل لديك مانع؟
راقب خطواتك، أهذا ممكن؟
أنا أتعلق بحياتي هنا
(حسناً، يا (شون
فقط تحدث معي
(قولي لي، يا (هانا
هل تأتين هنا كثيراً؟
!أصمت أرجوك
ليست هذه أفضل جملة تقولها
لتكسب اهتمامها
أنا أتحدث معها -
لا، يا (شون)، أنا لا آتي هنا كثيراً -
جاهز؟
أنظروا
أنظروا لكل هذا الصخر
ماذا؟ -
إنه صخر متحول -
صخر أخصر، عقيق أحمر، صخر مايكا
!الصخر -
... إنه في كل مكان، أنظروا إليه، أعتقد -
(تريفور)
(اذهب للحائط، يا (تريفور
لا أستطيع
لا يمكنني ذلك، الحوائط تتباعد بأسفل هنا -
حبلك مربوط بحبلي -
سوف تأخذنا معك لأسفل
لابد أن أفصلك عنا
ماذا؟ -
هانا)، لا) -
تمهلي، انتظري، انتظري، انتظري
لا تفعلي ذلك -
لا، لا، لا -
(عمي (تريفور
انظروا، يا رفاق، لقد وجدته
القاع بأسفل هنا
يا (هانا)، لقد كنتِ تعرفين ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
أليس كذلك؟
هانا)؟)
يا رفاق، ما هذا؟
يبدو لي وكأنه نفق منجم مهجور
إنه نفق (بلاجيلز) القديم
لقد تم إغلاقه منذ 60 سنة بعد كارثة كبيرة
كارثة؟
ما حجمها؟
واحد وثمانين من الموتى
هذا كبير إلى حد ما
هيا
!هيا، يا راعي البقر
تريفور)، هل كان هناك نفق كهذا في الكتاب؟)
لا، لا أظن ذلك
هانا)؟) -
نعم؟ -
هل يمكنني أن أسألكِ شيئاً؟
هل تتساءلين إذا ما كان أبوكِ وأخي ليسوا مخطئين؟
دعني أوضح لك شيئاً
أنا لستُ أبي
والعالم الذي كان ينتمي هو إليه
ليس له علاقة بي
أفهم ذلك، بالطبع
لم أكن أقصد أن أقول أنه عالمك
... أو أنه سيكون
أنت تعرف أننا ما زلنا نعد الساعات، أليس كذلك؟ -
أما زلتِ ستحاسبينني على هذا الوقت؟ -
سوف أحاسبك حتى أعود آمنة إلى بيتي
هانا)؟)
ما هذا؟
إنه المولد القديم الخاص بالمنجم -
أنتِ، يجب ألا تلمسي هذا -
ماذا تفعلين؟
ربما يوجد هناك بعض المواد المتطايرة
مولِّد خطير -
هانا)، هذا الشيء يمكن أن ينفجر) -
توقفي عن تشغيل المفاتيح
لا تفعلي هذا، لا، أنتظري
ابتعدي عن ذلك الشيء
حسناً، لقد تراجعتُ فيما قلتُ
هذا هو، أليس كذلك؟ أعني أن عمال المنجم
كانوا بالتأكيد يُخرجون أشياءهم إلى مكان ما
نعم -
هذه الطرق قد تُخرجنا من هنا -
يا (هانا)، كم عامل استطاع الخروج؟
واحد
هذه بداية
سأركب في المقدمة
ماذا؟ لا، لا، لا
هيا، لا تدخل هناك
لا نعرف إذا ما كانت هذه الأمور تعمل
إنها ليست آمنة
الممرات قد لا تكون آمنة
الطريق للأمام يبدو جيداً، اركب
يا (شون)، هذا لا يبدو آمناً
ما كنتُ لأفعل ذلك
... أعتقد أنني أرى شيئاً ما، إنه
أرجوك أخبرني أنه ضوء النهار
وإلا، فلا أريد أن أعرف
لا، إنه ليس ضوء النهار
إننا داخل صخور عميقة
ليته كان يوجد أحزمة مقاعد في هذا الشيء
هل أنت قلق بشأن أحزمة المقاعد؟
!احترسي
(هانا) -
أعرف -
اجذبي الفرامل، اجذبي الفرامل -
لا، لا تفعل ذلك -
لن ننجح
نعم
أحسنتِ صنعاً ، شكراً
يا رفاق -
(ابق كما أنت، يا (شون -
تريفور)، هل أنت بخير؟)
هانا)، طريقك انتهى)
اقفزي في مركبتي
ماذا؟
أسرعي، يجب أن تفعلي ذلك
فقط اقفزي -
أعرف ذلك -
مستعد؟
تريفور)، طريقك ينتهي أيضاً)
حسناً -
ماذا تفعلين؟ -
أريك الطريقة الصحيحة
لإنقاذ حياة شخص ما، هيا
أيمكنني المساعدة؟ -
حسناً -
مستعد؟
هل أنتِ بخير؟ -
نعم -
لحسن الحظ، أنا هبطتُ على شيء ليِّن
أنت تدين لي باثنتين الآن
من الذي يعُدّ؟ -
أنا -
ذلك ... كان ... رائعاً
ماذا حدث لكم، يا رفاق؟ -
لا تسأل -
ما هذا؟
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
لا تدخل هناك
ما الذي تتحدثان عنه، يا رفاق؟
يمكن أن يكون هذا هو طريقنا للخروج
هناك فتحة في الحائط
يا رفاق، انظرا
ياقوت
زمرد
فيلسبار
يا  رفاق، هناك المزيد
ماس
أحجار كريمة
... البلورات تتكون كثيراً وتوجد
في ... القنوات البركانية ...
هذا الأنبوب يمكن أن يعيدنا لأعلى، أليس كذلك؟
لسنا بعيدين عن السطح
(عندما أخرج سأشتري سيارة ماركة (ميزاراتي
(المال ليس الشيء الوحيد المهم، يا (شون
البشر مهمون أيضاً، كما تعرف
شيء من هذا القبيل -
(ليس لو كان لديك سيارة (ميزاراتي -
هل سمعتما هذا، يا رفاق؟
لا يتحرك أحد
أخبرني أن هذا ليس ما أظنه
(موسكوفيت)
وما هو (موسكوفيت)؟
إنه نوع رقيق من تكوينات الصخور -
ما مدى رقته؟ -
حسناً، رقيق جدأ لدرجة أن أقل تغير
... في الوزن أو الضغط
يمكن أن يجعله يتحطم ...
ونحن نقف فوق الكثير منه
!فقط توقف، توقف
حسناً، لقد توقفت التشققات
أريدك أن تمشي للخلف
من نفس الطريق الذي جئنا منه
بهدوء شديد جداً جداً، اتفقنا؟
دُس برقة
الكعب، الأصبع، أنت تحسن صنعاً
رائع، ببطء شديد
حسن، هيا
هكذا
عظيم
بحرص شديد -
استمر -
!لا
إنه في الحقيقة أسمك مما ظننت
!ما زلنا نسقط
تريفور)، ماذا يوجد في القاع؟)
... حسناً، لو كان ما كتبه (فيرن) صحيحاً
فهذه الأنفاق ربما تمتد لمئات، آلاف من الأميال ...
فيرن) لم يكن على حق)
تريفور)، أكمل كلامك، ماذا يوجد في القاع؟)
النظرية الأكثر احتمالاً أن هذه الأنفاق تنتهي وحسب
تنتهي؟ هل لديك أي نظريات أخرى؟
... حسناً، حوائط هذا النفق قد تكون قد تآكلت برقة
... بفعل الماء الذي ما زال يجري خلالها ...
مما سييجعل سقوطنا يتوقف تدريجياً ...
كنوع من الانزلاق المائي -
الانزلاق المائي -
حسناً، هذه إحدى النظريات
ولكن ألم يكن الماء سيصنع حليمات بارزة نحونا؟
سوف تنغرس بأجسادنا -
هذا ممكن أيضاً -
هل هذا ماء؟
نعم، ماء
إنزلاق مائي، إنزلاق مائي
ها هو قادم، تمسَّكا
!(شون)! (شون)
شون)، (شون)، هل أنت بخير؟)
لم تنغرس الأجسام المدببة بأجسدادنا
اتجه للصخور
أين (هانا)؟
!(هانا)! (هانا)
لقد كانت حقيبتي أثقل من اللازم
شكراً
إذن أين أخذنا هذا الشلال الآن؟
أصبحتَ تدين لي بواحدة فقط
يا رفاق، أين نحن؟
هل هذه نجوم؟
لا
إنه مجرد سقف الكهف
... هل هو أنا فقط، أم أن سقف الكهف
يتحرك؟ ...
نعم
... يبدو هذا حقاً
أليس كذلك؟ ...
إنها طيور
طيور كهربية؟
(إنها تشبه (سيانيس روزوبتيريكس
إنها فقط مضيئه مثل اليراع وحشرات سراج الليل
هذا مذهل
جميل
طيور ... متوهجة
هل رأيتَ هذه المخلوقات من قبل؟
نعم، في المتحف ولكنها كانت متحفرة
هذه المخلوقات إنقرضت منذ أكثر
من 150 مليون سنة
إلى أين هي ذاهبة؟
انظروا، نفق
يا رفاق، هيا
شون)، انتظر، انتظرني)
سيداتي وسادتي
أقدم لكم مركز الأرض
ماكس) كان على حق)
لقد كان على حق
!ماكس) كان على حق)
لقد كان أبوك على حق
كان على حق
هانا)، والدكِ كان على حق أيضاً)
... كلاهما كان يؤمن
بشيء كان الجميع يخبرونهما بأنه مستحيل ...
لقد كان على حق
ما هذا الضوء بأعلى هناك؟ -
لست متأكداً -
لابد وأنه تجمع من غازات مضيئة
لا أعرف
إنه مثل مربى الحيوانات والنباتات اليابس
مربى للكائنات الحية تحت القشرة الأرضية
بآلاف الأميال
عالم داخل عالم
الشلالات التي كان يمكن سماعها"
... منذ وقت طويل وهي تتدفق من بعيد
... أصبحت الآن تسقط على جدران الوادي الشاهقة ...
"تجري بمحاذاة الصخور بلا نهاية ...
(أعني أن هذا نفس ما كتبه (ليدينبروك
هل نقول أن شخصية (ليدينبروك) كانت حقيقية؟
وأنه كان موجوداً؟
لقد هبط شخص هنا
شخص رأى كل هذا
(شخص خرج وأخبر (فيرن
شخص خرج؟
هذا أفضل ما سمعته طوال اليوم
ألا يكاد هذا يذهب بعقلك؟
نعم، لقد ذهب عقلي بالفعل
فطريات عيش الغراب متحفرة هائلة
تقريباً نوع من الفطر العملاق
هل هذا يعني أن كل ما في الكتاب حقيقي؟ -
ربما -
والأجزاء الخطرة حقاً؟ -
لقد كنتُ أفكر في ذلك أيضاً -
حسناً
تريفور)، تعال بسرعة)
شون)؟) -
سأدخل -
نعم، انتظر -
أنت، أبطئ
سألحق بكما حالاً
هل كان يعيش شخص ما هنا حقاً؟
... ذلك الشخص
... (كان (ليدينبروك
أنظر إلى كل أدواته
... كل هذه الأشياء الحديثة
منذ قرن مضى ...
(ماكس)
(أنظر، يا (تريفور
(أعتقد أنني وجدتُ مذكرات (ليدينبروك
أنظر
يبدو أنه على الجانب الآخر من تلك الأشجار
يوجد نوع ما من المحيطات الجوفية
نعم
(لا أظن أن هذا خط يد (ليدينبروك
إنه خط أبي
تريفور)؟)
هل يمكنني أن أتحدث معك دقيقة؟
في الخارج هنا
هل يمكنك الانتظار هنا دقيقة؟
(انظر، أعتقد أنني وجدتُ (ماكس
أنا حقاً لم أجد الفرصة أبداً لمعرفته
أعني، ليتني فعلتُ ذلك
لقد كتب شيئاً ما وأنا أريدك أن تسمعه
"الرابع عشر من أغسطس 1997"
(اليوم هو عيد ميلاد (شون"
منذ ستة أسابيع، أخذتُ على نفسي عهداً
... أن أعود للبيت في الوقت المناسب
لكي أعطيه أول قفاز بيسبول يمتلكه ...
... والآن أنا قلق
ألا أجد الفرصة أبداً ...
لقد رحلتُ لأقوم باكتشاف مذهل
لأخبر به (تريفور) والعالم كله
... ولكن الآن، أنا مستعد لمبادلته
برؤيتك تكبر
... لكي تصبح الرجل الشجاع المتعاون ...
الذي أنا متأكد أنك ستكونه ...
(عيد ميلاد سعيد، يا (شون
أنا أحبك
"والدك
(الوداع، يا (ماكس
هيا
... (طبقاً لدفتر مذكرات (ماكس
نحن هنا في هذا الجيب الهوائي العملاق  ...
المحاط بالحمم البركانية
... وأثناء فترات النشاط الزلزالي الشديد
مثل التي نحن فيها الآن -
هذا صحيح -
المصهر البركاني المحيط بنا
يحوِّل هذا المكان إلى ما يشبه الفرن الكبير
هل هذه هو ما حدث لأبي؟
انظر، أنا أعرف أنني مجرد طفل
ولكنني يمكنني التعامل مع هذا الأمر، حقاً
اجلس
ماكس) كان يخطط للهرب)
مذكراته تقول أن درجات الحرارة هنا
يمكن بسهولة أن تصل إلى 200 درجة
والإنسان لا يمكنه أن يتحمل أكثر من 135 درجة
إنها بالفعل 95 درجة -
لقد كانت 82 عندما أتينا هنا -
درجة الحرارة ترتفع بسرعة -
إذن، ماذا نفعل؟ -
(أنا رأيي هو أن نتبع خطة (ماكس
:ها هو ما كتبه
... تحليلي لكلام (فيرن) الأصلي"
يقودني إلى الاعتقاد بأنه على الجانب الآخر ...
... من المحيط شمال موقعي الحالي
يوجد نهر يشبه الينابيع الحارة ...
"يمكن استخدامه للعودة إلى السطح
... لذلك، ما علينا فعله هو أن نعبر هذا المحيط
ونجد الينبوع الحار ثم نركبه ليصعد بنا لأعلى ...
لأعلى يبدو جيداً
الأمر أصعب من هذا قليلاً
يمكن أن ترتفع الحرارة جداً ويتبخر الماء
كم لدينا من الوقت؟
ثمان وأربعون ساعة
اثنان وسبعون على الأكثر
وربما أقل
:حسناً، السؤال هو
ما هي أسرع وسيلة لعبور المحيط؟
من المستحيل أن ندور من حوله
... لأنه لو مشينا على أقدامنا
ليس لدينا وقت
لا يوجد وقت لذلك
كل شيء موجود في الكتاب
هل أنتِ بخير؟
ما أخبار درجة الحرارة؟
إنها مائة درجة
(كل طعامك البحري، يا (شون
يجب أن نحتفظ بقوّتنا
أحسنت يا بنيّ
اسمع
ألا نحتاج لصارية في المنتصف؟
لا، لا نحتاج لها
الرياح التي نحتاجها بأعلى هناك
حرارية، إنها أسرع بكثير مما لدينا بأسفل هنا
أحسنت، أعتقد أن هذا سيفي بالغرض
أنظر، لديّ شيء لك
ما هذا؟ -
إنها بوصلة -
لقد كانت بوصلة أبيك
أنا أتذكر عيد الميلاد الذي أهدتها أمك له فيه
لقد كانت تريد أن تتأكد من أنه سيستطيع
دوماً أن يجد طريق العودة لمنزله
وربما تساعدك أن تجد طريق العودة إليها
(أشكرك، يا (تريفور -
هي لك -
هذا يعني الكثير بالنسبة لي -
وأنا أيضاً -
هناك شيء واحد يجب أن تعرفه
هنا بأسفل، الأقطاب معكوسة
... أقصد أن الشمال جنوب، والجنوب شمال
ونحن يجب أن نتجه للشمال تماماً عبر البحر ...
تقصد، الجنوب
بالضبط
حسناً، لقد بدأت الرياح تملأها
حسناً، امسكها، امسكها بقوة وثبات
حسن، حسن، حسن
حسناً، جاهزون؟ -
نعم -
!ثلاثة، اثنان، واحد، هيا
حسناً -
نعم، حسناً
نعم
هيا، هيا، هيا
نعم، استمر في الانطلاق
نحن ننطلق، نحن ننطلق
أنتما، هل يمكنكما انتظاري؟
حسناً، اركب
هيا، هيا، هيا بنا
لقد عاد
أيها الصغير
هل ترى تلك السحب؟
نعم
التيار يجذبنا في الاتجاه الذي نريد أن نذهب فيه
يجب أن ننزل الشراع
لا يمكننا ذلك
إن درجة الحرارة 109 درجة
ودرجة الحرارة تتزايد
نحتاج إلى كل السرعة التي يمكننا الحصول عليها
دعه مرفوعاً
إنها مجرد عاصفة صغيرة
ليست مشكلة كبيرة
هناك شيء يتحرك بأسفل
متألق ومن العوالق
إنه نفس الشيء الذي رأيناه عند الشاطئ
لا أعرف
يبدو أنه كبير نوعاً ما بالنسبة للعوالق
شون)، نحن لسنا في عالم البحار)
لذلك تراجع قليلاً
اتفقنا؟ -
أعتقد أنه نوع من الأسماك -
!لا
إنها في كل مكان
شون)، لقد أخبرتك أننا سنذهب للعب البيسبول)
اضرب بشدة
حسناً فلنرى ما حصلنا عليه
نعم، ضربة منخفضة سريعة
!(شون) -
هل تسمع شيئاً؟ -
مرحباً؟ -
(شون) -
أمي؟ -
أعتقد أن الاتصال سيء -
أمي، لا أستطيع سماعكِ
أين أنت؟
... عمي (تريفور) وأنا
... نحن تقريباً في رحلة صيد ...
هل تستمتع؟
توقف، لا، لا تفعل
عمي (تريفور) اصطاد لتوِّه سمكة كبيرة جداً -
شون)؟) -
هاتفي -
شون)، هل تعرف كيف تضرب ياليد اليسرى؟) -
جاهز؟ -
نعم -
خارج أرض الملعب
(شون) -
!احترس -
أنا أراهم، أنا أراهم
(شون)
لا، لا، لا تفعل ذلك
ابتعدوا عن الجوانب
انظروا ماذا يفعلون
إنهم لا يريدوننا
إنهم يريدون السمك
اسمعا، (شون) امسك أنت بالمقود
ونحن سنمسك بالحبال
هانا)، امسكي بحبال الشراع)
شون)، هل تريد أن تأخذنا يميناً؟)
ماذا؟
من ذاك الطريق
هيا
حسناً -
هذا جيد -
الآن دعيها بهدوء
دعيها تفلت بهدوء
دعيها ببطء
هذا يفلح
نحن نبتعد عنهم
(أنت عظيم، يا عمي (تريف
هذا ما أقوله للوسط العلمي منذ سنين
(هانا)
دعيني أرى
الحبال
لقد أمسكتُ به -
(شون) -
(شون)، لا تفعل هذا، لا يا (شون)
!(شون)
!(لا، يا (شون -
!(تريفور) -
!(شون) -
تمسكك -
!لا تدعه يفلت
لا
تريفور)؟)
مرحباً؟
أيها الصغير، أين نحن؟
قل لي، هل تعرف أين يمكنني الحصول
على بعض الماء؟
أنا أتحدث مع طائر
لابد وأنني بدأت أصاب بالجنون
!(شون)
انتظر
الرياح قذفت به في هذا الاتجاه
أما زلنا نتجه شمالاً؟
نعم، ما زلنا نتجه نحو الشمال
إنه طفل ذكي، إنه يعرف الخطة
أنا متأكدة أنه سيكون بانتظارنا عند النهر
هيا نبحث عن النهر
أنت، انتظر
أين ذهبت؟
أحسنت
حسناً
والآن أي طريق؟
الجنوب
هذا جيد
النهر في الشمال
حسناً
انتظري، دعيني آخذ هذه
لا، لا، أنا بخير -
هيا، دعيني آخذ هذه -
تريفور)، أنا بخير) -
هانا)، (هانا)، لقد أخذتُها) -
دعينا فقط نتوقف ثانية
اسمع، سوف نجده
اشربي هذا
هل هذا آخر ماء لدينا؟ -
نعم -
سوف نحتاج إليه، احتفظ به
هانا)، اشربيه)
هيا
!اخفضي رأسك
ما هذا بحق ...؟ -
ماذا كان هذا؟ -
نبات ضخم آكل لحوم؟
(هانا)
هانا)؟)
!تماسكي عندكِ
من الذي يقوم بالعدّ ، أليس كذلك؟
نعم
من يبقينا في المسار، أليس كذلك؟
أفهم هذا
إنه مجال مغناطيسي
مستحيل
صخور مغناطيسية؟
!لا، لا، لا، لا، لا
!لا، لا
جرِّب ذلك بدون أجنحة
ها هو النهر
الينبوع الحار لابد وأنه داخل هذا الكهف
!(شون)
أين يوجد هو؟
أين ... يوجد ... هو؟
تريفور)؟)
!يا إلهي، ليتني حقاً قرأتُ ذلك الكتاب
لا أراه في أي مكان
تريفور)؟ (تريفور)؟)
انتظر دقيقة
ماذا تفعل؟
أنا ذاهب لأحضر ابن أخي
(هانا)
هذا ... كله خطئي أنا
فلتنجي بحياتك
فقط اذهبي للمنزل
... سوف أنتظرك عند النهر
لأطول مدة ممكنة ...
لماذا فعلتِ ذلك؟
تحسباً لما يمكن أن يحدث
!(شون)
!(شون)! (شون)
!هيا
!يا إلهي
كم أنا سعيد بلقائك
نعم، وأنا أيضاً
هل أنت بخير؟ -
نعم -
يجب أن نذهب
انتظر، انتظر، انتظر
هل هذا هو الينبوع الحر؟ -
نعم، هذا هو المكان الذي سنذهب إليه -
هيا
ألم ترى ديناصوراً من قبل؟ -
ليس وعليه جلد -
إنه سريع جداً
لن ننجو
تريفور)، ماذا تفعل؟) -
(هذا حجر (موسكوفيت -
شيء وقعنا فيه من قبل
من المستحيل أن يتحملك
ولا يستطيع تحمله أيضاً
هيا اجري
!تريفور)، لا)
(إنه لن ينكسر، يا (تريفر
استمر في الجري
إنه سيلحق بك -
أعرف ذلك -
استمر في الحركة
تريفور)، لقد نجح هذا)
!احترس
!(تريفور)
لقد تذكرتُ شيئاً
أنا أكره العمل الميداني
تريفور)، هيا)
... لقد بدا وكأنه ... وأنت بدوت وكأنك
نعم، أعرف، لقد كنتُ محظوظاً حقاً
حسناً، من هذا الطريق
هذا، سيء
وهذا، أسوأ
هيا بنا
النهر
كيف سنصل إلى الينبوع الحار؟
الماء يغلي -
نحتاج شيئاً يطفو -
... أي شيء، يمكنني استخدام كتلة خشبية أو
ما نحتاجه حقاً هو قارب
من الذي كان يطالب بدوره مرة ثانية؟
هيا، اقفزا
إنها أفضل مرشدة جبال على الكوكب كله -
هذا صحيح -
أنتما حقاً لم تكونا تعتقدان أنكما ستفزعانني
أليس كذلك؟
يجب أن تعملا بجد أكثر من هذا
للأسف سوف أتقاضى منك
المزيد من المال على هذا
هل يمكنني أن أفتح لديكِ حساباً؟
ما هذا؟
ليس هذا جيداً، إنه قاع النهر
الماء ينفذ منا
يجب أن تتمسكوا بشيء ما
... هذه الرحلة ستكون إلى حد ما
مليئة بالمطبات
هل الجميع بخير؟ -
نعم -
أين نحن؟
ما هذا الضوء بأسفل هناك؟
إنها الحمم البكانية
إنه المصهر البركاني، إنها ترتفع
المفروض أن يكون هناك ماء في هذا النفق
بخار، ماء يندفع لأعلى
لقد تأخرنا على الينبوع الحار
لم نلحق به
ماذا نفعل؟ -
هل لديك أي اقتراحات، يا بروفيسور؟ -
بدون ماء، لا يوجد بخار
وبدون بخار، لن نذهب إلى اي مكان
هذا المكان يبدو أنه بلا ماء منذ ساعتين أو ثلاثة
ولكن الحوائط ما زالت مبتلة -
هذا مستحيل، درجة الحرار ة 130 -
تريفور)، خلفك) -
ماذا؟ -
إنه مبتل
إنه بارد
هناك ماء خلف هذا
يجب أن يكون هناك ماء
خلف الجيب الهوائي أو خلف النهر الجوفي
تريفور)، إنها تقترب)
أنظروا، إنه ماغنيسيوم
إننا ننزلق -
كم طلقة مضيئة بقيت معكِ؟ -
ثلاثة
ماذا تريد أن تفعل بهم؟
سوف نشعل الماغنيسيوم
عمداً
انتظرا
!يا إلهي، إنه مبتلّ أكثر من اللازم
يجب أن أهبط لأسفل أكثر
أعطيني واحدة أخرى
امسكوا بساقيَّ
هيا
ستضطرون إلى ربطي بحبل
يجب أن أنزل أكثر
تريفور)، إنها تقترب)
هذا جيد، حسناً، استعدوا
إنها الأخيرة
!تريفور)، احترس)
ما رأيك في هذا؟ -
أكثر قليلاً -
أسرعي
لأسفل أكثر؟ -
أكثر قليلاً -
حسناً، توقفي
هيا -
هيا، اشتعلي
هيا
(هيا، يا (تريفور
ما زالت مبتلة، سنضطر إلى قذفها للجانب الآخر
ماذا؟
لا
!لا
تريفور)، هيا)
تريفور)، هيا) -
لقد اشتعلت، لقد اشتعلت -
!اجذبوا
اجذبوني لأعلى -
بسرعة -
اجذبوني لأعلى، اجذبوني لأعلى
هيا، اجذب، اجذب -
اجذبوا -
!احترسوا من الأسنان، احترسوا من الأسنان
!شون)! هيا)
انخفضوا، سوف تنفجر
هذا الشيء تزداد حرارته
!أعرف
!تمسكوا -
!صدقني، أنا أتمسك -
هل هذه هي السماء؟
!تمسكوا، جميعاً
!توقف عن قول هذا -
!إنها تخرج تلقائياً -
(هذا جبل (فيسيوفيوس
(اسمع، يا (شون
... لو سألَتك أمك ماذا فعلت في نهاية هذا الأسبوع
(قل لها أن عمي (تريفور) أخذني إلى (إيطاليا ... -
إيطاليا)؟) -
شون)؟)
ماذا؟ لقد أخذتُ فقط بعض العينات الجيولوجية
بعض العينات الجيولوجية؟
بعض الأرطال من العينات؟ ولكن ماذا تتوقع؟
أنا ابن عالِم
أنظر، أنظر
خذ أنت هذا
خذ أنت، نحن آسفون
أتريدون الانزلاق مرة أخرى؟
الانزلاق جيد، إنه جيد
كل ما تريده
لماذا كان هذا؟
الآن، نحن متعادلان
ليونارد)، لقد عدتُ)
توقف عما تفعله
وما الذي أفعله؟
أنظر
أنت تبحث عن عمل
... لا داعي لذلك لأنك لديك وظيفة
(في معهد (أسجيرسون آندرسون
للاستكشاف التكتونوفيزيقي
أسجيرسون آندرسون) ... ماذا؟)
ما زلتُ أبحث عن إسم جيد
ولكن المهم هو
أن المد يرفع كل القوارب
يا رجل، هذا رائع
أعتقد .. هل أنا قارب؟
أنت قارب، سنعود للعمل -
حسناً، يا صديقي -
حسناً، حسناً، حسناً
علام كل هذه الإثارة؟
يا (آلان)، كيف حالك؟ -
بخير -
ماذا تفعل؟ -
أنا؟ -
أنا أنتقل إلى معملي الجديد
الأهم هو، أين كنتم؟
سمعت أنك فوّت محاضرة يوم الإثنين
وكل طلابك قدم شكوى
لقد كنتُ في أجازة سريعة
أفضل ما قمتُ به
هذا مثير
ستعدني أن تحكي لي عنها، اتفقنا؟
لستُ متأكداً إن كان لدي وقت
(ولكن يمكنك أن تقرأ عنها مجلة (ساينتيفيك أميريكان
ساينتيفيك أميريكان)؟)
أنظر، أود فقط أن أقول لا داعي
لأن تحمل لي ضغينة، اتفقنا؟
بشأن نقل المعمل وموضوع التوسع هذا
أنا في الحقيقة أبحث عن مبنى خاص بي على أية حال
كيف ستفعل هذا بالضبط، يا (تريفور)؟
حسناً، فلنقل أنني سقطتُ على ثروة صغيرة
إذن غداً سوف تصبح كندياً
نعم، يبدو هذا
سأقول أنه قد حدث بيننا ترابط رجولي قوي
في وقت قصير جداً
ما رأيك أن نأخذ بضعة أسابيع في المرة القادمة؟
عدة أسابيع؟
ماذا ستفعل في أجازة الكريسماس؟ -
لا شيء، أنا غير مشغول -
لقد وجدتُ هذه في أشياء أبيك
اقرأها
مدينة (أتلانتيس) المفقودة
سنتحدث
شون) ما هذا؟)
أنا فقط أُطعم حيواني المدلل -
أي حيوان؟ -
(شون)
هل تعتقد أن أمي ستسمح لي بالاحتفاظ به؟ -
لا أعرف -
ربما حتى لا يبقى هنا
أنظر إليه -
أنت، هيا -
هذه هي مشكلتك -
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟ -
لديّ لك بعض الطعام، هيا
عد هنا
هيا
تمت الترجمة بواسطة
Dr kalid
kelbanhawy2000@yahoo.com
مراجعه وتعديل نهائي
جــاكــ79ســبــارو